

Jovan Dupkarski

O Home: 1000, Skopje, North Macedonia

Email: <u>i.dupkarski@gmail.com</u> **Phone:** (+389) 70336259

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jovan-dupkarski/

Gitlab: https://gitlab.com/jovan_dupkarski/my-work

Date of birth: 29/05/1992

ABOUT ME

Hello I'm Jovan, Full Stack Developer with nearly 2 years of experience in developing and maintaining web and software applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.is, Node.is, Typescript and MySQL. I also have significant experience with PHP and Laravel gained with the projects and programming challenges during the academy for Full Stack Development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[20/05/2022 – 30/09/2023] **Full Stack Developer**

Sourcico

City: Skopje

Country: North Macedonia

- · Develop and maintain web applications using modern JavaScript technologies and frameworks such as React.js and Node.js with Typescript.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to implement UI/UX designs, ensuring the technical feasibility of design concepts.
- Build and maintain RESTful APIs and backend services, ensuring smooth data flow and integration.
- Optimize applications for speed and responsiveness, delivering a seamless user experience across devices.
- Stay updated with the latest trends and advancements in web development, integrating new technologies as appropriate.

[01/01/2022 - 20/05/2022]

ICT Sales representative

King ICT

City: Skopje

Country: North Macedonia

Develop and convert sales opportunities into sales of computer hardware, software and

ICT services

[05/2020 - 31/12/2020]

New Business Sales Executive

Slice

City: Skopje

Country: North Macedonia

Actively seeking out new sales opportunities through cold calling, networking and social

media and selling company's products and values to them

[05/2018 - 08/2019]

Regional Sales Manager

Fitofarm Plus DOO

City: Skopje

Country: North Macedonia

Managing the sales for the eastern and western regions of the country. Market research, Organizing weekly and monthly promotions, In-Store presentations, Involved in the decision making about new product designs and promotion materials.

[03/2016 - 05/2018]

Pre Seller Representative

Nelt ST

City: Skopje

Country: North Macedonia

Sales Agent for the brands of Procter & Gamble and HiPP

Arranging, visiting, selling and charging per customer according to a specific routing plan. Finding new and improving the connections with the existing partners and customers

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[09/2011 - 07/2015]

Marketing

University of National and World Economy

City: Sofia

Country: Bulgaria

[20/04/2021 - 01/03/2022] **Full Stack Development**

Brainster https://brainster.co/

Address: 1000, Skopje, North Macedonia

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): English, Bulgarian, Serbian

DIGITAL SKILLS

Full Stack Development

HTMI & CSS | Javascript / Typescript / Node / Express | React.js | Bootstrap | jQuerr y | MySQL | Git | PHP Laravel

Digital Certificates

Google Digital Garage: Digital Marketing | Advanced Google Analytics